James Gibson

I am a hard working, diligent individual with an excellent eye for detail and a firm grasp of technology. In the two years since I left college, I have worked at numerous places, both voluntarily and on a temporary paid basis. I have spent the time between these jobs practicing in various fields of the IT industry, particularly hardware related support. I also administrate an IRC server which at this time has 6000 users. I have assembled computers for people, including my own. I've also dabble in other areas (programming etc)

Key Skills:

- It Literate: Able to use both Microsoft packages and more advanced software
- Highly Organised: Able to prioritise tasks and work to strict deadlines
- Flexible: With the ability to adapt to changing environments
- Self Motivated: Able to rise to most challenges and work to the best of my ability
- Knowledge of hardware: I am capable of solving most problems that are hardware related
- Engrossed in the industry: I check various IT/hardware news sites daily, and as such am up to date on innovations that happen, when they happen.

Employment History:

Synergy Farm Health

Data Inputter

Approx 2 months overall, from 2011-Present

Duties involved transferring information from paper forms into an Excel database, which included designing said database and typing up Vet's notes. Other duties were processing tax rebates, invoices and delivery notes to ensure the correct amount of money was being transferred, etc.

The Old Schoolhouse Mid 2011 to Late 2011.

Farmhand

Duties included repairing fences, putting up wiring to protect trees in the orchard, cleaning out sheds, washing the vehicles down with a pressure hose, transporting lumber into a storage shed and general garden maintenance such as weeding and mowing the lawn. Also involved was laying hedges to stop the livestock escaping.

British Heart Foundation F&E September 2012 - Present

Volunteer

Duties range from assisting customers in their purchases, arranging deliveries/collections and

maintaining the shop floor to a decent standard. They also include moving furniture to and from the shop floor when it is sold/received.

Education:

Holyrood Sixth Form/College 2009-2011

AS levels in: Critical Thinking, Sociology, Psychology and Communication and Culture Studies.

Holyrood Academy 2004-2009

GCSE'S in: English Language [A*], English Literature [A*], Mathematics [B], French [B], Science [C], Certificate in Digital Applications [B], Religious Studies [D] and Electronics [D].

Interests: I enjoy reading a variety of books, outdoor leisure (primarily cycling or walking), My main interest is, to be slightly over-arching - anything related to computers. I have, as said above, dabbled in most areas, primarily hardware and programming. I have a working knowledge of C#, Javascript, python and C++. I have working knowledge of a few Linux distros and obviously of Windows, although I have yet to try Windows 8. I have dabbled briefly in Mac.

References are available on request.